<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Thukral Brooms</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_open">Open navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_close">Close navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="nav_header_title">Android Studio</string>
    <string name="nav_header_subtitle">android.studio@android.com</string>
    <string name="nav_header_desc">Navigation header</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>

    <string name="menu_home">About Me</string>
    <string name="view_allbooks">View All Books</string>
    <string name="create_book">Create Book</string>
    <string name="view_ownbook">Own Created Books</string>
    <string name="menu_share">Share</string>
    <string name="menu_send">Send</string>
    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>

    <string name="our_mission">Bringing the world a better way to clean through innovation design and quality
    For over 60 years, The THUKRAL family has made quality their utmost priority. “Shri Krishan Lal Thukral” started The Thukral Company in 1960 with one mission; to make the finest, most durable wire-wound Grass and Coco brooms. Shri Krishna Lal son Mr. Kamal Thukral Ji and grandson “ Udit Thukral Ji” have since  expanded that mission to include the finest Brooms and cleaning tools.
</string>


    <string name="starting_up">Bringing the world a better way to clean through innovation design and quality
    For over 60 years, The THUKRAL family has made quality their utmost priority. “Shri Krishan Lal Thukral” started The Thukral Company in 1960 with one mission; to make the finest, most durable wire-wound Grass and Coco brooms. Shri Krishna Lal son Mr. Kamal Thukral Ji and grandson “ Udit Thukral Ji” have since  expanded that mission to include the finest Brooms and cleaning tools.
</string>

    <string name="advance_in">During the height of the Great Depression, Shri Krishan Lal son Mr. Kamal Thukral Ji joined his father in the broom making business. They added a new generation of ideas and energy. Although times were hard, the son looked to the future and he modernized operations and built a second plant in Kundli, Sonipat – Haryana</string>

    <string name="thukral_in">Twenty years later the 3rd generation, Mr. Udit Thukral has come from aboard after complete the study and looking towards the future. Udit Ji focused on expanding distribution in the retail and commercial markets with the Thukral Tea and expanding into the National market with the entire Thukral line. While working on growing distribution, they continue to focus on quality, national advertising, service and product innovation.</string>

    <string name="aboutus">Mission-We believe in providing the finest , most durable brooms and cleaning tools to keep our environment clean And healthy.
In 1960 ,Shri Krishan Lal Thukral along with his father Lala Faqir Chand Thukral started the Thukral company with a goal to provide the finest , most durable wire wound grass and coco brooms . Its a quality driven organisation and  providing with the best quality have been their utmost priority.
Mr Kamal Thukral  the son of Krishan Lal Thukral and his grand son, Udit Thukral further joined their family business and has now expanded the company by modernising operations, innovation and by being open to new and flexible ways of working.Over the years they have gained immense expertise in supplying and trading . By delivering effective outcomes  They have been able to build trust, networks and partnerships, thus leading their company to be top most in their market.
Their services are courteous , responsive and regulate in a fair, proportionate and transparent manner.
Right in the commercial heart of India , they have their outlet of Grass and Coco broom in Lahori gate, Naya bazaar in old delhi.
Mr Udit Thukral after completing his Bachelor Degree in Business Administration , went further to pursue knowledge in International Business Management from King’s College ,London.With all learnings and experience, seeing all the success over the years , they decided to further expand their business and brand name in the retail and commercial markets with the Thukral tea . Further expanding their distribution and spreading into the national market with the entire thukral line, they continue to focus on quality, national advertising ,service and production innovation,Thus making their brand the best !</string>

</resources>
